Hello everyone! We are Meow Meow Call Choice!
Yes, yes! So, it looks like you guys can see us today?
It looks like we're at the beach for a bit,
What's the plan today?
You ready?
Yes! Today's project is for the members who love to scream.
Let's play at Sea Paradise!
We are at Sea Paradise in Hakkeijima!
Thank you very much!
I'm so happy!
Yes, it's a reward!
Just the other day, our first concert was over,
We are here today with the members who love to scream,
Today, we have a member who loves to scream!
Sea Paradise is a great place,
We are going to have a lot of fun at Sea Paradise today!
Yay!
All of you!
You're in the picture!
Sea Paradise has an amusement park and an aquarium,
Ao is the main musky, so everyone wants to go there!
I'm really looking forward to it...
My voice is rattling...
So looking forward to it!
Looking forward to it!
Excited!
Fun!
Let's go have fun!
There's so much! So many things to do!There are so many! There are so many things to do!
This place is so big, let's go on a roller coaster right away!
I love roller coasters!
Let's have fun together!
Let's go!
Let's go on the roller coaster!
I like it. Your accessories are very nice.
It's an accessory.
Matching accessories.
It's a new song.
It's our new song.
I'm sure, Aoi, you should listen to it.
Where can I listen to it? I don't know.
Please come to our live concert.
Matching accessories
This is how we do it.
That's right.
We've been having a lot of laughs lately.
Thank you very much. It's you guys.
03-04.
Let's go.
Yay!
You like it, don't you?
Everyone got together with their favorite members.
I'm happy.
I'm looking forward to it.
Yay!
I have to talk.
We have to talk.
We're a little bit on the listening side.We're a little bit on the listening side.
I know someone who specializes in listening.
I know what it's like to be a listener.
Let's bring out Alice today.
I'm excited.
This is great.
Exciting.
I'm excited.
Isn't it a surprise to your fans that Aoi can ride in a real-life situation?
Not really.
I can do anything. Anything.
Just make sure all your belongings are safe.
Make yourself at home.
People are taking pictures.
The Status Coaster is big, but I didn't get a shot of it.
What's Mr. Levi?
It's written right here.
It says that's his name.
Mr. Leviathan.
What's Mr. Leviathan?
Like Mr. Blue?
Certainly.
Okay, I'm going.
I'll go to the front.
I'm going to line up.
Let's go!Let's go!
hahaha
De-tele-tele-tele-tele
Camera
It was just a moment ago, sir.
De-telegraphy-de-telegraphy
It happened a little while ago
Oh, it's leaking
It's leaking!
Wait, it might be right past the boarding gate!
What should we do?
Wait, oh no!
Wait, I'm not ready to regret this.
You won't regret it.
Riglet.
Riglet?
You're a smart girl.
Do you think amusement parks are still fun no matter how old you get?
Yes, it is.
Will you still be coming with me when you're 80?
I'll still be riding roller coasters when I'm 100.
Would you still come with me?
Yes, I will.
Can a 100-year-old ride a roller coaster?
Sure, sure.
How old do you have to be?
You know, there were some new free songs at the first concert.
What was so fun?
I have a knack for fighting even when I lose.
Alice.Alice.
It was fun! I had so much fun since I was free!
I'll do my best!
Alice was so cute!
So cute! Ali is cute!
That was fun.
What else do we have here besides roller coasters?
What? What else is there?
The haunted house.
If you say so, I'll give it a try.
I wonder what kind of system it is.
I wonder if it's pretty heavy.
I don't know.
But I want to ride all of them anyway.
There's the water one.
Good job, guys. The concert.
Yes, I guess so. Thanks for your hard work.
Shall we toast? With airs.
We can toast when we make our debut.
That's right. I'll leave it till then.
Anyway, thank you very much for your hard work.
We've decided on your debut,
Thank you very much.
I'm glad you're getting 8 cages right off the bat for this.
Let's make it a reward.
Let's do it.
Today's a bad day. Because we have the whole night.
We'll be together from morning till night.
Together.
Oh, wow.Oooh.
I have to talk.
I don't know what to say.
Can I go to Alice's office?
Sure.
Knock-knock. Excuse me.
I'd like to talk to you about something today.
I'm sorry, what is it?
I don't know what I'm supposed to say in a vlog-type video.
Alice-sensei, please help me.
Yes, I do.
But I think it's pretty important to say something tangible.
I see.
For example, a roller coaster.
Like, "This is big.
"Oh, it's big! It's big, isn't it?
The weather was not too hot today.
I thought it would be cooler.
I thought it would be comfortable.
I see.
You are very strong. Alice-sensei.
I'll try defiance.
Thank you very much.
I don't know what to do.
I thought I really don't usually talk.
Me too.
Alice, you're right, I have an image of you as a good listener.
I've always been on the listening side.
I enjoy listening to them.It's fun to listen to.
Fun. I understand.
Listening is more fun than talking.
Yes, yes.
Sometimes I get it.
I get it. I get it.
I get comfortable with it.
Even now.
Here he comes.
I know, I know.
Will you go back to Kansai dialect?
When you get your Kansai dialect back.
I will.
How's that? But I've been using it for a long time.
I've been using it for a long time. Hakata dialect comes out a lot.
Yes, but probably even more than before.
Oh, that's true.
I think I'd say I feel like I'm already using it.
I love Hakata dialect because it's cute.
I love Hakata dialect because it's cute. Really.
I usually have to avoid speaking in Hakata-ben in front of the members.
Well, let's just keep it up.
Is it coming out?
It's coming out.
If you laugh, it's unconscious.
Unconscious.
It's cute.
Alice and the others, even though they are from Kansai or Osaka, they really hid their Kansai dialect from the moment we met.
I was like, "How did you manage to hide it?
It's like, "How did you manage to hide it?I was like, "You know what?
So why don't you just let it out more?
You want to let it out? I don't know, I just can't get it out.
I don't know.
It's like, I have to get it out in the environment.
Now that the dye is coming out.
But...
There are other members from Kansai and other places.
Yes, yes, yes. So it's true, it's true.
It might come out when we talk together.
Something.
I went out to eat with Man-chan the other night.
What? I didn't eat.
What?
Are you sure?
What? I didn't eat.
You ate some kind of crepe.
Oh, yeah.
Ehhhh.
Laughing.
Scary.
They put that crepe thing in there.
Oh, is there something like that?
There are a lot of couples and students who are going to some kind of gathering or something.
So, if Julie and I were to go to the gate, where would you take us?
Ehhhh.
I want it to be quiet, so I'm going to the cinema.
Movie theater?
But I also think that if I were to go to Rays with Aoi, I would go to a planetarium.
I've never been to a planetarium.I have never been to a planetarium.
I haven't been to a planetarium since I was in elementary school, when it was like a school class,
Sometimes it reminds me of it.
Oh, there is the best one on the Great Tokaido Highway.
I'll go there.
But the amusement park is the best.
I want to go to the amusement park.
It's coming.
Let's go!
Let's go and jump.
One, two, three.
Jump.
Pappan.
Please.
Wow.
The battlefield.
Aoi and the others.
They're the members who love to scream.
I'm so happy.
I'm looking forward to it.
I'm going to go public with Callan TV.
I'm going to get on it and make it public.
Public.
If there was a camera here, I would have cared about my face,
Since there isn't.
I want to scream.
I don't know. All of it, super-zoomed in.
All of it.
The clothes wrapped around my shoulders and legs.
I'm going to enjoy it.I'm going to enjoy it.
Yay. I'm looking forward to it.
Looking forward to it.
Excited. I'm looking forward to it.
I'm looking forward to it.
I'm working on a bug right now.
It's the first one I did.
I can see all the way to the end of the castor,
I should go up, but I can't see the bottom and the car flies away.
It's fast.
Wow.
Thank you very much.
s rehabil ored
nly had it.
prince It was delicious... in the old days... Yoroshiku Siri
It's so beautiful.
The view, the ocean is so beautiful.
I was going to burn my eyes out, but...
My eyes were burning so hard!
It was a lot of fun.
Earlier, when we were all climbing the top of the roller coaster
Congratulations on your debut!
and "Good job!
as we rode the roller coaster.
I really felt that the concert was over.
It's over!
I still don't feel it yet.
I really don't.
I see aces and things like that, you know, sometimes.I see aces and stuff, sometimes.
IMHO
I kind of miss the standing charts and stuff.
I can't erase the position list.
Oh, I know.
Tête-à-tête, tête-à-tête.
Hey, a map?
What's there?
Oh, that. Let's go to the Haunted Mansion after.
We're going to the haunted house?
You're going to the haunted house?
Yuka, are you going?
Alice, can you go?
Me, but I don't have much experience.
Oh, I see...
Okay, well, I...
I want you to pinch me.
Let's go to battle. Battle.
Oh, you're so strong.
There are brave warriors.
Can you guys make it to the haunted house?
We're heading to the haunted house.
Bye-bye.
Good night.
Oh, man, the view is awful.
Shocking horror.
I hope you all feel like you're in an amusement park with us!
It's noisy like this.
Wait a minute, I'm scared.Wait a minute, I'm scared.
It's so dark.
I'm sure that in a few more minutes, the oldest will be the only thing holding on to the oldest.
I'm definitely gonna hang on.
It's okay.
I'm excited, I'm excited, I'm excited, I'm excited, I'm excited.
Waku waku waku waku waku.
Wait, I have no idea what it's going to be like.
We've got bug repellent and everything.
Really?
Because Ayumi...
I'm scared.
Scary, scary, scary.
This one surprised me the most.
It's real.
Ayumi's friend
Friend of Ayumi
No, oni yanma
Onii-yanma, the insect repellent
It's like a picnic to this area
Like a picnic
It'll be there soon.
Can you see it?
I can see it.
I'm a little scared.
Scary, scary, scary, scary.
Please, please
I'm scared. I'm scared. I'm scared.
Wait, maybe I'm scared.Wait, I might be scared.
Maybe Ayumi's fine.
I'm fine.
Easy to explain...
but I can't imagine it at all.
Me neither.
Well, just hang in there.
I got a lance.
So you're going in?
Yes, I'm going in.
I'm in. - Okay.
It sounds really, really scary.
It's scary. I don't know.
I don't know.
It's a little scary.
I think it's leaking.
That's funny.
What?
What? Wait, it's already started?
Wait, wait, wait, it's already started.
You're scaring me, Miya.
I'm scared.
It's okay.
Check the video.
I'm scared.
Please, please, please...
No, no, no, no!Oh no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
It's not penalty day, is it?
It's not penalty day.
What? I'm scared.
I'm scared. I'm scared. I'm scared.
No, no, no.
No.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Wait, wait, wait.
Laugh.
Laugh! Laugh!
This way.
Forward, forward.
Forward, forward, forward.
What happened to Nakabayashi?
LOL!
Laugh!
I don't know.
Alice is too flat.
Alice, why are you going in front of me?
Can you go? Can you still go?
Yeah, I can make it.I can do it.
I can do it.
I'm going.
LOL!
is jeden
re
kate
and
it's not
Squalls for everyone.
If I can see it from here.
If you see it, we'll see it.
We have to find it.
Oh, wow.
Oh, go, go, go, go, go, go.
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
Go, go, go, go, go.
We have to go now.
I have to go now.
Wah!
Oh!
I'll get the diner.
They're coming in!
Wait, I feel like I'm losing a lot of energy.
Alice, you're amazing.
I'm better than I thought I'd be.
Really?
I screamed.
Alice was so supportive.Alice was too good to be true.
Oh, my God, I can't believe it!
What should I do?
Murayama! Tickets!
I can't do it!
What should I do?
I'll be in the penalty game!
I've been hiding it all this time.
Let's just do it with Alice.
Yeah, we'll go together.
I think I'm going to have to ask you to go with me.
I'm exhausted.
You fell at the end.
Riko, too.
She fell backwards at the end.
I'll take a little bit of this, too,
From the inside,
A little bit at a time,
Vanilla flavor,
I was already so close,
Oh, oh, wait, I'll take that one,
Oh, this one's cute,
This one, I'll take this one,
Cute,
Cute. I'll take that one,
White lucca meat,
I'll get it,
Congratulations,Congratulations,
Cute,
Cute, but I'm going to eat it now.
I'll eat the ball.
What's that?
Yeah, thanks for the potato.
Oh, Daddy's coming over here.
Nice.
I'm going to mash it.
He's getting beat up.
He must be close.
Wow.
We all knew on a daily basis that this brave daddy was out there.
He's coming at us fast.
Hey, hey, hey.
I don't know, there's no friendliness here.
Wow.
No friendliness.
It's so unfriendly. Yuukani.
Amazing.
Yuuka, raise your eyes.
Amazing. Yuka's full speed.
I don't think about it anymore.
I can't stand it.
I'm scared.I'm scared.
Baby.
It's okay, baby.
That's it. Thank you for watching.
Now we're going to ride the water attraction.
That was delicious.
It was delicious.
It was a bit of a dove and scream lunch.
You were screaming, weren't you?
The pigeons love you, too.
She gets tired of it.
Probably.
I was really tired.
At the souvenir place.
I got one or two stuffed animals for each of us.
That's nice.
HIRAKA?
She just passed by.
Where?
I'm in the crevice.
Look, it's swimming.
It's big.
It's swimming.
It's great.
Oh!
Hard at it.
It's new.
The dolphins are doing their best to stay alive.
Can't wait to go see them.Let's go see him soon.
Ho-ho-ho!
Even the dolphins are doing their best to stay alive.
Oh, something.
This is it!
That's what we're looking for.
It looks like it's going to get wet.
It's a wet attraction.
Wow!
It smells like water.
Oh, wow!
Oh! This is definitely fun!
Wait a minute.
Oh! I'm sure!
100% sure!
This summer is here.
It's gonna be hot.
Whew.
Hot enough for me already.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten.
That's it.
Done.
Ta-da!
Wah!
Ai.
Wow.
Wow.Wow.
Alice's fashion today.
What do you think?
Oh, I'm sorry.
Thank you for explaining.
Go ahead.
You're looking good.
What's it like?
I'm kind of into this stuff lately.
I'm into street style.
It's cool.
It looks good on you.
I tried it on.
Thank you.
And I can work out.
Is it bad?
No.
It looks good.
Wait a minute.
Let me out of the car.
Let me out.
I'm off.
I'm not dressed for the wet today.
I'm looking forward to it.
I wonder how wet I'll get.
It's been so long since I've been to a wet attraction like this.
I'm excited!
I'm off to get wet!
Good luck!Good luck!
We're on different teams, aren't we?
Yeah, we're on a different team.
I'm off.
Like this.
That's right.
This is my Alaza Sky.
In.
This is my
Alazar Sky
In
Ooh!
Like a water roller coaster now.
Yup.
Okay
I'm off.
So I heard it's gonna be really wet.
You ready? You ready?
I'm ready.
I'm off.
Don't go.
I'm going.
We're almost in the middle. Thank you.
I'll put the bed on.
Well, have a good day.
Have a good day.
I'm off.
Whoo!Woo!
That's great!
I'm kind of in the water right now, and the hot water is still plopping right now.
I still feel like I'm splashing around.
This is fun. The hot water is making me sleepy.
Wow!
I'm being swept away.
It's going too fast.
Suddenly it's getting faster.
It's going fast.
I'm getting wet.
It's good. It's good. It's good.
Oh, my God.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
I'm wet, I'm wet, I'm wet.
I got all wet.
Last, last, last.
I'm getting a little bit tired.
Wait a minute.
I'm about to make a mistake about the future, aren't I?
It's a little close.
Wait a minute.
That was fast.
Wait, wait, wait.
I didn't hear you.
You're way off.
I'm not listening. I'm not listening.
Is this okay?Is this okay?
Wait.
It's not the one that was so peaceful.
Yay!